Good evening, everyone.
Yes, I'm Director Murahoshi, and I'll be proceeding today.
This is the 184th edition of Uguka's Delightful and Uneventful Showroom. We have decided on a subtitle for this edition, and we'll be delivering it again this time.
We will decide on a subtitle with the users here, and then we will deliver a program based on the subtitle, which is an original rule of Ucka.
What shall we do today?
What is this? Is this how you did it?
What shall we do?
Today is the first showroom in June.
I feel like it's been a while.
That's for sure.
I haven't done it since the last time I did it with Ma-chan.
No, that's not the last time.
No, it wasn't.
That was last time.
Last time.
It's been May.
What?
That's the last time. It's been about as long as Mar-chan.
Liz has been on the show a lot.
Recently.
Selected members.
I wonder what would be good.
I wonder.
You haven't gotten the tweets in yet, right?
Oh, that's right.
But there's a typhoon coming.
Oh, yeah.
Liz answered just now.
There's some kind of typhoon, you know, with a name. Always.
I told her that typhoons have names.
I thought it was interesting.
I thought it would be nice to write a letter like that.
It will be released in June.
The rainy season will blow away with Uka-dekka. We won't be defeated by the typhoon. Good evening.
Good evening.
It's 2023 and a half, that's not good!
Will there be no more voices saying it's bad?
That's for sure.
That's a good idea.
Good, good, good.
I'm open to anything.
We're halfway through 2023.
If we do it in July, we're halfway there.
Is that right?
Yeah.
That was exactly six months!
So close.
Then you're close. You're not even close.
Tune tail delivery.
We're hungry.
But we're hungry too.
Just now.
We ate a lot.
I can't believe a typhoon.
Oh, wait. It's like a typhoon that goes around and around and around and around and around.
Then, let's do this. Let's do this.
Okay, well, let's see, I'll write.
I'll write it. Please.
Typhoons go round and round.
Don't you miss "Gururukyan-dokan"?
I miss it.
Typhoons go round and round and round.
You were dancing.
I was dancing.
What's that?
Maybe it's a generation gap.
It's like, "Round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round.
That makes me happy.
Oh, it's normal.
What's missing?
Hey, it's sad.
Eh, we all know that.
Eh, some kind of medium.
Eh, YouTube.
TV. Television.
Educational programs.
Educational program.
Well, you know, um...
Is it okay if there's a "ba" in it? Is it okay if it's a "ba"?
This... this... this...
Oh, yes. This, this, this.
Oh, I won!
This, this, this.
Is it pretty?
Yes, it's cute.
Marukashi's.
The state of the Marukashi.
Yes, yes, yes.
I get it.
It's the worst.
Let's go then.
Then I'll write the title where today's subtitle is decided.
I'm pretty much the only one who thinks so. Sorry, sorry.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
I'm Yukari, Ukka.This is Ukka, Yukari.
Okay, showroom.
All the typhoons are going round and round and round.
Well then, good evening once again, everyone. We're Uka. Pleased to meet you.
Today's new con, I, Muraho Series, will bring you today's new con. Please give my best regards.
Well, then, please come in.
I am Yume Kawashiro. Please take care of this.
Yes, I am Mao Surisawa. Pleased to meet you.
Yes, I'm home.
Thank you very much for watching the 184th Uguka no Yukari no Funna Showroom today.
I would like to take this time to spread the word.
In order for as many people as possible to see this broadcast, I'm going to tweet about it on Twitter. So, that's all for now,
What should I do? What should we do?
This one? Okay, then.
I like it.
I don't know if many people can tell what it is.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do. What should I do with my comment?
I don't know. If I make it "Gurudokan", it will be a bit like "Bakuri".
I'll just think of it as "Dokkan" for real.
I see. So it's OK.
If it's a bang, it's OK.
Isn't it OK? Let's have it be "Bokkan".
Then, why don't we just have it be a "boom" in the winter, too?
It's hot, isn't it?
I think we should have all typhoons go round and round with a bang.
I guess so. Let's have the titles, then.
I'd like all the titles, please.
It's written above, but if all the typhoons also come Gurukyan Bokan,
Thank you very much for the boom.
Bokan is OK.
Yes, "Boom" is OK.
Then what should we do when it comes?
Boom.
It's a bang.
Let's go when it comes.
Oh, here it comes!
Okay!
What kind of couple?
Like that girl?
That girl?
That girl.
This girl.
Five, four, three, two, one.
One. That's it.
I hope you will all retweet this.
Now, let's go to the free talk.
We, Wook, will be releasing our first major single "Wonder Little Love" on June 21,
Wonder Little Love" will be released on June 21,
The lead song, or should I say the title track?
The title track. The music video for the title track, Wonder Little Love, has been released.
Congratulations.
I know, right? I knew it was going to be released later at the last showroom.
Liz, you do this a lot.
I might do it for sure.
I don't have any particular reason.
I just go round and round.
I'm just saying I'm going to go round and round.
Wait a minute.
I'll get right to it. Well, I mean, many of you may have seen it,
Let's watch the music video of Wonder Little Love together again.
I haven't watched it with everyone yet.
That's right.
This is the first time to watch it with everyone.
I guess we can talk about some points.
Yes, that's right. Let's chat about that as we watch it.
Let's watch the music video for Wonder Little Love!
I'm sleeping. I'm sleeping.
Oh, and here comes A-chan.
What is this? A fireplace? The one taken under the fireplace.
Oh, wait a minute. He's waking up his hand.
I see. Yes, yes, stop!
I'm wearing Momo-chan's clothes at the part of Reeses now, too. But since Momo-chan is coming out this way, I'm coming out this way so that I can see a little.
Oh, wait. Wait a minute.
I'm back, I'm back, I'm back!
Oh, my face!
Here, here, here!
Can you see it?
This is because Momochan is in front of me,
And then from the right side, like this.
Oh, you mean like this!
Then I can go like this.
Thank you.
I want you to pay attention to this.
Oh, interesting! That's amazing! You can do this?
That's great OK.
I was looking at it with my eyes so much!
Hello.
Oh, you went a little bit like this. It's like this.
Hmmm.
Nice.
Yes, sir.
We went through quite a lot of dance scenes.
We went through it.
I knew she was cute.
Two, four.
She's 23 years old, and she fits in perfectly.
Amazing.
Ha-ha-ha.
Class points!Class Point!
Class point!
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's drawn out!
Oh, my,
That didn't look good.
It's a little off.
This, this?
It's a dreamy portrait.
Lulie sings a song called "Dreaming Portraits.
And they're all doing the "yes cheese" thing.
like a "yes cheese". But Ayumi's not in it?
Yes, she's in it. This character piece.
Her eyes are closed.
That's right.
Before that, do the heart.
He's making a heart around Lulie.
I'm making hearts around Lulie.
I was going to send it off with a slambonction.
Aah! I closed my eyes!
I'm doing the "galoon galoon" thing...
I didn't have a point.
The point is that he is making a heart.
The point of the moment, and the portrait from there.
The point is that they are all taking a picture together and taking a portrait.
That's the point.
Shall we continue?
Yes.
That's great.
Luna, what's wrong?
I didn't see it.
I did see it, but, you know, when I look at it again...
It's true.
Yes, yes.
I'm sorry.
Depending on the concert or something.
I've had them wink at me at some live performances.
You mean during Moa-chan's solo, right?
Oh, this is it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Isn't she cute?
It's a little bit broken up.
You're not wearing pink, are you?
If you do it live...
You're welcome, too, A-chan.
Depends on the day.
Please look forward to it, depending on the day.
You're right, Mia-chan, you're a featured artist.
OK. Excuse me.
Here it is.
Yes, stop. Yes, please.
This is what we're doing here. What do you think you're doing? Doing this. Yes, what do you think I'm doing? This.
Let's recruit some people. Luli's imaginary, imaginary, imaginary thing,
What do you think the other five are doing? I'm drawing a picture. It says "drawing.
I know what a picture is, but are you drawing a picture? I mean, well, I mean, pictures, or writing, or....
There are no dishes. This one. It doesn't look like a dish. It's not a violin either.
Shikishi (colored paper). It's not colored paper. I'm drawing something, but what am I drawing?
It's a picture of something you want to make come true, right? That's right. That's something we all share later on, right here. That's right. I wonder what they are drawing.
I wonder what they are drawing. What are they drawing? What are they drawing? What am I drawing?
A dream. It's surprisingly hard to know, isn't it? What do you mean by dream? I'm drawing a dream.
Dreams? You mean you know the Chinese characters for dreams? Isn't it very fast?
It's difficult. I'm drawing a dream. Fist circle. Drawing a heart might be a little too close. It's a little too close.
You are drawing a definite thing, aren't you? That's right. Each of us is in charge of one thing.
Laughs
Love.
Really?
My name.
Your own name.
I see.
LOVE!
Oh.
I can lie.
Yes, you can.
Oops!
The correct answer has appeared.
Well, let's go.
Let's go. The correct answer.
The correct answer is, what are we drawing?
It's UKKA.
Yes, let's see, first of all, I am in charge of U of UKKA.
I am.
That's what I'm writing.
I am in charge of the second one, K.
Yes, that's me.
That is, I am in charge of the second K.
That's right. And Sora is in charge of A,
Everyone is in charge of hearts.
The player in Sora is Uka Heart.
I write "Uka heart.
That's right. That was kind of close, wasn't it? The heart one.
Right. That's right.
Don't you want me to write this at a live performance?
It could be the member in front of you,
Or even your guess.
You want me to write it?
Trace it together?
I want you to trace. I want you to trace.
Like you're following me.
Yes, that's right. That's weird. It looks good. It's white.
But, you know, me and Momochan, K, we write at different speeds, don't we?But, you know, me and Momochan, K, we write at different speeds, don't we?
It's true.
K. Writing speed.
Sei-no.
Oh, I'm fast.
Right.
So, that's part of it.
Sure, I'm sure. That's one of the highlights.
Adjust your speed according to your guess.
Yes, that's right. It's a highlight. That's the highlight. That's the point.
Like that.
Yes, it is. Thank you very much.
Yes. Please do.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
It's a honeydew clover.
You were warned by your teacher today.
How do I do it?
Like, "Get up close.
They're a little far apart, so I don't know what's going on,
So he asked me to move them three closer together,
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
We made adjustments, right?
Yeah, yeah. I thought the clovers were a little too far apart today,
There it is.
It was there.
It was there, so today,
From now on, let's make sure that we can see the mitzvah properly,
I'm going to do it.
We are doing it.
And the three of them are singing,
I don't know,
Chimi found this clover.
This is it.
That's it. What's this?
She's drawing a clover.
She's drawing clovers.
There are four, aren't there?
Yes, yes.
Yes, that's right.
So this is what it looks like when you do it with both hands.
That's right.
Ha-ha-ha.
I see.
That's good.
You have a lot of points.
Then, please continue.
Oh, yes.
That's good.
That's good. Here.
It's cute here, too.
It's cute.
You know, the live version and the PV version of the heart song are different, aren't they?
That's right. The choreography is different.
I like it.
Your wife went a bit here, didn't she?
She did, didn't she?
Yes, she did.
I feel like I'm being sucked in.
Good job.
I made it.
Oh, I winked.
This, you know, was kind of sauteed rai.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was the last one to be taken.
Yes, I had some extra time, right?
It was used stiffly.
This place is cute, isn't it?
I like it here.
It's cute.
I like it here. This hair is cute.
Oh, Yuri, this is the point!
Too cute~.
Thank you very much. I looked at it again, and there are so many points.
There are too many, you know.
I was able to tell you a little bit about what we, the pictorial artists, are drawing,
I hope that when we do it again at the next live concert, you will be able to see it while thinking, "Oh, I was drawing that,
I hope that when we do it again at the next show, you can look at it and think, "Oh, I was drawing that.
How was it? What did you think?
Oh, they say it's cute.
Does it look really white and cute?
It's kind of like a new chandelier, though it's more like a Uka-esque one,
It was cute.
Yes, it was. It's refreshing and I'm glad I got to see the details.
It's full of Uka's paintings.
It's great.
Cute. Thank you very much.
The choreography of Wonder to Love, you know, you choreographed Imaginary Travel last time,
You did it today, fancy travel.
Yes, we did it today.
Haruka-san, who choreographed it, choreographed it for us.
Harukan-sensei.
This is Harukan-sensei.
She's super cute.
Really cute. Thank you again.
Thank you very much.
This time, Wonder to Love, and TikTok, too, a little bit,This time, Wonder to Love is, and TikTok, too, sort of,
I'm doing my best, right?
You're doing your best.
That's right. We came up with a TikTok-like choreography,
Yes, we all thought of it together.
For everyone?
Not that one? Not me? This one.
I heard some rumors.
Really?
I'll tell you the story behind it.
Yeah, I'll tell you.
Wait, wait.
I'm doing Hello Hello, a real dyed-in-the-wool world.
I've been thinking. What should I do with this dyed-in-the-wool world?
The dyed-in-the-wool world was a little difficult. The way it was performed.
When I thought about what to do, I thought, "There is such a thing as dyeing with love.
Ai Dyeing.
There is such a thing as "aizome", right?
Yes, yes. Ai puts ink in a tray and dyes cloth.
A world of dyeing.
And it's just the two of us, alone under our own roof, thinking up ideas.
Everyone is alone in the world, and it's really messy.
That's why it's no good. This was a place where we couldn't think alone.
If it's dirty, we can't decide.
Because we'd be fooling around.
You've been thinking about it for a long time.
I thought about it, but it was so silly that I couldn't come up with anything.
That's right. It's so cute.
There are other videos on Uguka's TikTok of her dancing individually, with two people, or with the whole group,
I would like to invite you all to dance as well, so please take a look.
Please take a look.
And on May 28, you held a release event at Morissia Tsutanuma.
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Who is Morissia Tsutanuma?
This one.
This track.
Crepes.
It was crepe day.
This is the second time I've seen Morissia Tsutanuma, I think.
It's nice that it's the second time.
Thank you all for coming to visit us.
It's always hot here, isn't it?
It's hot.
I wonder if it's because it's inside. It was winter last time.
Was it raining this time?
That day. It's not raining just yet.
It was raining last time.
But the people on the second floor of the shopping mall and the shopkeepers were really enjoying the show, and I was very grateful to them.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
The next one will be on Saturday, June 3.
Thank you for your time. I won't be there.
Otsu.
Both of them had a completely different world view, but their charm was overflowing.
It was spilling.
It was hard to believe it was their first time at the tip.
It was amazing.
I learned a lot from them.
Yes, there were.
I learned a lot about Ultrasoul.
Ultrasoul.
I learned a lot from Ultrasoul.
It was a lot of fun.
Yes, it was.
Everyone had a great time.
Yeah, they were. Everyone was.
I'm glad, I'm glad.
I'm glad to hear that, and thank you again for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
When I look at their tips, I wonder what I'm going to do.
I know, I know.
I know, I know. I know. I know.
It hasn't been decided yet.
It hasn't even been decided.
It hasn't even been decided yet.
I'm starting to think about it.
If there is a decision, but not at all, I wonder what happened the other day.
That's right. That's right.
That's right.
It makes me feel a lot of different things.
I'm glad. But we made it safely.
We were both so nervous.
You seemed to be having fun.
I'm happy for them.
It was a good venue.
Ultrasoul was great.
It was great.
Thank you so much, Seita.
The next day after that was June 4. We did it similar to the release event Salt Stop Salt Festival.
This was your first venue here, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It was at a place called "Underground Walkway. We held the event on an underground walkway,
We were really grateful that people other than Uguka's fans stopped by to see the event,
I was really grateful for that.
I think I felt that the most at Ladybug.
Yes, that's true. That's for sure.
I was really grateful for that.
Hagendazs day, right?
I remember that. I remember Sunday.
They were giving away a lot of Hagendazs.They were handing out Hagendazes in a big way, weren't they?
I heard.
We didn't eat it, though.
I guess it was pretty crowded.
The members were also doing Hagen-Dazs at another home.
Like Hagendazs, there was a lot of trouble that day, too.
I wish I could see you in costume.
You took it.
Yes. I was doing Hagendaz, and Rina-chan was in front of me.
Rina-chan was so badass.
She was terrible.
She was wearing a hoodie and eating spaghetti.
She was eating spaghetti with mint sauce.
I thought she was fine because she was wearing a hoodie, but she jumped on the hoodie, and when she took it off, it went through the hoodie.
It was all over my costume.
I was wondering how not to get mad at the manager.
He had already caught it once when I was there, and he was like, "Why are you still in your costume? Rina-chan.
But Rina-chan was wearing a hoodie too.
She went through the hoodie.
So we did this together.
I thought it was possible, didn't I?
It was so easy.
We were able to get both of them off safely.
Because we had Zaket.
We're going to make it.
Put it on. Let's eat.
We'll talk about the backstory of the re-live.
You might be filming for TikTok on this day, right?
That's right. They were pretty open to it.
A lot of recommendations were flowing in.
So what? Me too.
It's great, isn't it?
I heard that I should put a Wonder Altrab song on my post,
So I made one and posted it.
Then, a lot of people did it,
I thought, "Thank you very much.
It's also good for fans to post with each other,
I've been doing it for a long time.
I would like you to take pictures with everyone,
I hope you will recommend it to others and ask them to listen to it.
Thank you very much.
I will continue to work with Lily from now on,
Please come and visit us. Please do.
Is that about it?
Yes, that's about it. Okay.
Then I would like to come to the project.
So the subtitle of the project is "Typhoon and everything goes round and round with a bang"?
Yes.
Let's go.
Let's find a generation gap word like "GURU-GURU-BUKAN"!
New.
Let's comment on words that Kasetsu and Murahoshi know and only Moa doesn't know,
Let's play and feel the generation gap.
Let's find the opposite word, Moe-san.
Moe-san.
Moe-sa.
Moe-moe-cun's.
Only Moa-san knows.
We don't know.
I see.
I wonder.
You mean from the comments section?
Think for yourself.
I wonder.
I won't explain what it means.
Me and everyone else's generation.
I'm the only one who knows.
Huh?
Can I watch a TV show or something?
No, it's fine.
You know what?
Blueberry School.
I don't know.
I don't know why.
Why don't I know?
Why don't I understand?
It's difficult.
It's hard.
What's it called?
It's not, is it?
Borderline.
I don't know.
Do you know what it is, Mr. Kakoe?
Of course.
Only one Softbank.
I don't know.
Me neither.
Mr Barrie?
I don't know.
What's Mr Barrie?
Mr Barrie?
Mr. Barrie?
Is that what you mean?Oh, is that what this is about?
I don't know.
Chobeligu.
It's kind of, like, bubbly.
Oh, MK5.
I know this one.
You don't know? You don't know? Oh, is it a TV show? Yeah, no.
You don't know MK5? My, my, my, my, my, ma, ma, ma, ma, MK5, MK5.
MK5, Liz! What? Liz! Generation? Generation? It's not a generation!
It's a word that stands for something.
Oh, I don't know. Music Five?
Music, MK5.
5FIVE is five seconds ago.
Oh, 5FIVE is, eh, 5FIVE?
5FIVE?
You mean five seconds ago?
What's the one before that? Something, something, something.
Five seconds ago.
Are you seriously in love?
No!
It's MK5, right?
Oh, it's called MK5.
You say "5 seconds ago" in a song?
There's also a song called "5 seconds ago".
Oh, I see.
I think I'm seriously in love.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What do we have here?
Mixi. I know it.
Have you heard of it?
Mixie, I know.
You know Piramikki?
Oh!
Oh, it's, uh... it's educational?
Educational? This?
I don't think it's educational.
It's more like a variety show, like a children's variety show.
You know who was on it?
I don't know.
Like, uh, Hanniyasan.
Ah!
And Pon-san.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ah! They seem to be the same. It looks like he's wearing...
Gym clothes! He's wearing a gym shirt.
He's wearing it, he's wearing it, he's wearing it.
You know Stretchman?
Gymnastics?
No, I mean, maybe you're judging.
Do you know Stretchman?
I've heard of Stretchman.
Seriously?
Doesn't that come up a little bit? Stretchman?
Where?
He doesn't come up?
It's a stretchy, stretchy stop.
What?
No?
It's a stretchy, stretchy stop.
I don't know.
What about exago? I know Exigo. I miss it so much. I used to watch it a lot.
I've heard of it. But I really don't know what it's about. Really?
I know what it's about. What kind? What kind?
It's a show. It's like Vanna EP or something. I think it's a character.
Exigo. Exigo. Why?
Why?
It's a quiz show. Is it faculty-related? I haven't heard anything about it.
What? Like Chusuke Kami.
Ralai? Even Lalai knows about this, right? We've been talking about it.
Do you know Laralai? The comedian?
Yes, yes. Oh, yes, yes.
Ralalai?
Round and round.
Oh.
Yeah, I know.
You used to dance when you were in the sixth grade or something.
I know what you mean.
Electronic man
Electronic man.
Electronic Man.
Electronic Man
Do we all have something in common?
Of course.
You like trains?
You take pictures.
Like electric trains?
Train boys?
You mean like playing with trains?
I don't know anything about "Densha Otoko".
I've never heard of Train Man.
I've only heard of Yukio Otoko, but nothing related to men.
Train Man, Train Man.
If there was a story, actually.
Actually.
It's a popular movie on 2ch.
What's the story?
A guy who's not very popular gets a lot of advice from 2ch and makes a wish.A popular guy gets a lot of advice on 2ch and makes a wish.
Why a train man?
Is he someone who likes trains?
You missed it, didn't you?
Ah, the famous
Generation
I had a train driving encounter.
So that's what you mean.
What should we talk about?
Remember that one?
It's educational.
The "dun, dun, dun" thing?
The spinning thing?
Oh, my God! I've heard of that! I know what it is!
There's like a net nearby.
You just drill a hole in it.
Like this...
Crush it.
And then you turn it.
I'm sure you've seen this before.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Spin, spin, spin, spin.
Kukkuk.
Aah!
Oh, my gosh! Your hair reminds me!
I'm sure I saw it! I definitely saw that!
Oh, my God.
That's hard.
That one, that one, that one...
Like acorns.
What's an acorn?
Acorns?
Hani hoheto iro hani hoheto iro haloito heho nihon hakuitte.
Wow.
I'm serious.
I'm practicing right now.
I know Ina Barwah.
Yeah, I know it.
I can't explain it, but I know it.
Pause.
Pause?
Try it, Momochan.
What do you think?
Inabarwar.
Inabarwah.
Oh, is that a popular pose?
It was a popular pose.
Yes, it was.
It's a popular pose.
No?
Uh-oh.
Was that a popular pose?
I don't think that's your voice right now.
Oh, that.
This...
Who does that?
Who's on high alert?
What's the right answer?
The correct answer is...
Shizuka Amagawa, figure skater.
Shizuka Amagawa.
She's a figure skater.
Her hands go behind her back.
Not at all.
Like that.
Okay, this is it.
I don't know.
Gap-disnarration gap.
No, but it's funny.
I'm trying to remember...
I know what it is, but I don't really remember what it's about.
I don't really remember what it's about.
I've heard of it, but...
I'll try it again.
You've done it.
Thank you very much.
Okay, so...
The next corner is here.
Breathe together... the Guru Guru Boom game.
Oh!
On my cue to start.
Close your eyes, cover your ears, and count 10 seconds.
After 10 seconds, say loudly
Let's say "Guru Guru Boom" in a loud voice.
If the three of you are in sync, you should be able to do it.
You're all in sync, aren't you?
Okay, okay.
Sounds like a lot of fun.
Let's say we're going to start getting ready.
Close your eyes and count for 10 seconds.
Ten seconds in your mind.
Okay, okay.
Do this with your hands.
After 10 seconds.
Boom, boom, boom.
Round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round.
You can do it, right?I can do it.
We're good. We're good.
We're all breathing together, for sure.
That's a given.
Then may I ask you to shake it?
Here we go.
Ten seconds.
All right.
Thank you for watching.
Group of groups!
Boom-boom!
Eh, that was a little close.
Eh, hey, Mo-chan and I are pretty close.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Ayama-san is pretty good.
About 10, 9, 8.
No way!
2, huh, the same, same.
No, it's not the same.
Wait, I want to do it again.
Do you want to tempo? Tempo.
Which way do you want to go?
I'm going to count from one to ten.
Let's start at one.
Let's go early, BPM early.
Okay.
G-G-G-KHAN.
What?
Giggle, giggle! G-G-G-Googly!
Huh?
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
That was fast.
One, two, three.
I did it five times.
Really show them once what tempo you count at.
Common.
It's done.
The current one was like 1, 2, 3,
But now it was 1, 2, 3.
One, two, three, four.
Okay, let's count to one.
Okay.
Just like when you were using it.
I miss it.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Boom, boom, boom.
10, boom, boom, boom.
10, it's like "Sue.
Not "10, boom, boom, boom.
10, boom, boom, boom.
Put a V in it.
That's it.
10, go round and round and boom.
Just give it a little twist.
I think I can do it next time.
Here we go.
One, two, here we go.
All right.
Don't be scared!
Be scared!
What are you scared of?
You scared me!
You scared me.
Oh, that was close!
That was close!
A little late.
A little too late.
That was close.
But it was close.
Well, it was a little bit close.
That was horrible.
That was super-serious.
Next time, you have 10 seconds of free talk.
I can't do it.
So, are you okay with groups or what?
I'd love to be in a group.
Let's just keep doing it.
What do you want to talk about? Let's decide on a topic.
A talk topic?
Ten-second talk topics?
About your favorite number.
It's not complicated, is it?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let's do it.
Let's start.
I like 5.
Oh, I like 5.
I like 4.
Oh, 4.
Oh, like 5, 4, 3.
Oh.
Ahhh.
Aaaaah.Aaaaahhh.
I made it.
I made it match.
I just did.
But it's too late.
Ehhhh.
But maybe it's too late.
Wait, wait, I want to do it again.
While talking with my eyes closed.
I see, because I'm going to match them, right?
I understand.
So you want to change it up a bit?
What should we do?
Let's change it.
How to spend a rainy day.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's do it.
I get up at noon and spend the rest of the day lazily.
Oh, you're the lazy type, huh?
I have a round face!
I was surprised.
I have a curly face.
Well, I thought that was enough.
It might be a little difficult.
How was it just now?
Measure.
I didn't even measure it.
Oh, it's like, "Does it fit or not?
Everyone else was looking at me while taking measurements.
I'm the one with the round face.
I introduced myself.
Oh, I'm so embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed.
Ooooo.
This is the last.
This is the last one.
Which way do you want to do it?
It's difficult if you close your eyes. You'll be surprised.
It's better if you don't close your eyes.
I'll introduce myself.
Okay, 10 seconds of talk without closing your eyes.
What do you want to do? What's the theme of the talk?
What's your charm?
Okay.
Aww...
Aww... Aww...
Wow, wow, wow.
Yes.
I like eyes. I like big eyes.
Eyes.
Long eyes.
And I, um, moles, I guess.
It's been more than 10 seconds, I'm sure.
It's hard.
It's difficult.
The eye line.
Nakayama.
It's really interesting.
I think I remember that.
Thank you.
Oh, no.
Not bad.
Oh, 1,000 people are watching.
Thank you very much.
Wow, 1000 people have already heard about it.
I'm embarrassed.
Oh, it was fun. This is the most fun thing to do, isn't it?
It was fun.
What am I doing?
Sorry.
You're right.
It was fun. What's this thing you keep calling me? What is this? That's rude! Don't be like that. I'm serious. I'm serious.
I'm tired.
You're early! You haven't done anything today. I'm just counting dolls.
I was saying "kuruguru no can" and it was already the end of the show.
I didn't know there was such a program.
We also talked about swimsuit videos today.
That's true. That's right.
We have done a lot of things. So, the ending came quickly.
Now that we're in, we have this. Thank you.
Here you go. This way.
Not this way. Here is the schedule for the upcoming release of the first single "Wonderland Love".
Saturday, June 10, at Raraport Tachikawa Tatehito,
June 11, Sunday, at Kamenwei Hongkourok,
And Friday, June 16 at Tower Records Shinjuku.
This one is that one, isn't it?
I like it.
It's a talk show.
Aren't you impatient?
Wait a minute. I was wondering what happened if you hadn't mentioned this, but I thought I saw it.
OK, it's already on.
It's already out.
I saw the talk show and the, what do you call it?
I saw it.
There will be mini-games, so I hope you can come and have some fun.
After that, on Saturday, June 17, I will be at Laraport Shin Misato,
And on June 20, we will be at Shibuya Magnet rooftop,
Please come to the release events. Please come to the release events.
You will be at Furagemi on June 20, right?
Yes, that's right.
So I hope you will come to the hate time, too.So I hope you'll be here at hate time.
Maybe at night.
It's nighttime.
I'm sure.
It will be at night.
And,
And then,
Friday and Saturday, July 14 and 15,
Fishbowl and I will have a 2-man live in Okinawa, Japan.
Okinawa.
Yay!
The venue is Output Okinawa, so it will be the first time for us to go to Okinawa,
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm wondering what to wear and what to wear.
It's early.
I'm in the process of deciding.
Please come and visit us on our first trip to Okinawa.
And the day after the 2-man live in Okinawa,
On Sunday, January 16, we will be performing at Spark 2023 in Yamanakako.
The venue is Lake Yamanaka, and during the Lake Yamanaka Exchange Festival, there will be two performances, so we hope you will come and enjoy the show.
I think people who come to Okinawa have to come to Okinawa before this,
That's right.
It is like Okinawa up to this point.
It is a set.
We would like you to make an expedition with us.
Let's spend some time in kazosuke.
Yes, and there will be Uka's 1-man live.
Saturday, September 30 is at Shibuya Beats,
and Saturday, October 14 at Tokyo Kirima Club,
And next year.
Sunday, January 21, 2024,
Uka's 3 one-man shows are scheduled for Sunday, January 21, 2024 at Ebisu Liquid Room.
Please come and join us.
Tickets are not yet available,
I just have the schedule,
If you know someone who might be interested, please come out and join us.
If you are interested, please come out.
I'm interested in you.
Skippy.
Come with Skippy.
Uka's one-man live.
People who are interested in him.
You might know him.
Like a date.
You're curious about Uka.
Please invite her to come and play with us. Please do.
Please do.
I guess that's all.
I would like to confirm the top 5 final ranking.
Fifth place.
Yes, 5th place, thank you, President Frog.
And 4th place, thank you, former Ryujimao homeroom teacher.
And thank you Kazuchan-san for No.3.
Thank you very much, Shubarie-san.
And thank you Harisaku-san for 1st place.
Thank you very much. I have an important announcement.
It is an irregularity. Next Thursday, June 15 at 7:00 p.m.
Thursday?
I'll say it one more time, Thursday.
Next Thursday, June 15 at 7:00 p.m.
Thursday?
Thursday!
So please take a look at what we have in store for you.
The last one before release?
The last before release.
This will be the last distribution before the release of the first major single, so please watch it.
To make sure you don't miss any of the streaming, please register it as a favorite by clicking the heart mark.
We also have all of our personal feeds, so please check them out.
This concludes the 184th edition of Ukka's Delightful Showroom.
This episode?
None!
So, this is the end of Ukka's showroom.
Please come back next week.
That's all for now!
After 10 seconds, close your eyes, cover your ears, and say bye-bye in 10 seconds.
OK.
After 10 seconds we all say bye-bye.
Like 1, like 1, like 2, like 3, like 4, like 5, like 6, like 7, like 8.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
OK.
OK, with breath.
Okay.
Bye-bye!